# MIRANDA DICKSON

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER** 

11011 Andenwood Drive Austin, TX 78726 **t:** (512) 786-2761 **e:** mad12a@acu.edu

e: mad12a@acu.edu w: madsgraphic.com

## **EDUCATION**

 Bachelor of Science in Graphic Design & Advertising Abilene Christian University 2012 -2016

# **SKILLS** (PROFESSIONAL)

- · Adobe Creative Suite
- · Microsoft Office
- · Graphic design
- · Logo and branding design
- · Print design & production
- · Web & UI design
- WordPress
- Squarespace
- · HTML (code manipulation)
- · Google Suite
- · Video Editor
- · Social media asset design
- · Time Management
- · Customer Service
- Photography
- · Photo editing

### **AFFILATIONS**

- · AIGA (Contributor)
- National Youth Leadership Committee

# **HOBBIES**

- · Theatre
- Fencing
- Archery
- Gaming

# **PROFILE**

Austin, Texas has been my home, and through its community and culture, I became involved with the fine arts, both visual and performing. The creative approach I use is about being laconic with design. The audience should understand the who and the what of a company from their design.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Graphic Design & Website Associate**

Texas Library Association, 2018 - Present

- Expanded the new brand with over 30 pieces of print and digital collateral for corporate, marketing, and events using Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.
- Created ad presentations from ads sent in by our sponsors and organized them to showcase each company. The scroll was a success that gained more recognition for these businesses in the main hall. I utilized PowerPoint, Keynote, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.
- Coordinated with my supervisor and our website developer to design and format digital
  assets and UI elements for the updated WordPress website and established an
  organization style.
- Stepped up as the art director for the 2018 winter issue of the Texas Library Journal (and the following four journals) and was able to complete it in 4 weeks.
- Took on a new role as a photographer at the 2018 Annual Conference for the Libraries Transform Texas photo booth while guiding volunteer staff.

#### **Graphic Designer (Contract & Freelance)**

Advokate, LLC, 2018

 Established two logo variations from a simple project brief to distinguish anew lifestyle coaching business using Adobe Illustrator.

Sinful Monarchy, 2018

 Established unique social media accounts (Twitter, Instagram, Twitch, etc.) and developed behind-the-scenes content for the new game released by an indie video game company.

The Connection Movement, 2017 - 2018

 Organized the client's collected images, voiceovers, and music to create a few advertisement pitch videos to make a clear and excellent first impression with Premiere Pro.

**ENTERFACE Forms, 2017** 

 Started brand design from the ground up to create a logo, iconography, and UI design for the mobile interface.

SUTIWABY Productions/ Urban Monk, 2016 - 2018

 Put multimedia designs and content into place for the start-up. The multimedia included branding, merchandise, Squarespace websites, and online videos. I took on the new role as a social media co-manager by developing social content and exploring analytics.

The Next Lab, 2016

 Transplanted Illustrator web design files into Photoshop and organized the materials to aid coders and developers. I took the opportunity to design a variety of sign-in pages for ScaleFactor to use for the new website launch.

#### **Internships**

Austin Film Festival, 2018 Manic Kat Records, 2017 - 2018